http://www.la/privacy

Please wait...
LoginSign Up
Shopping Cart (0)
Free QR Code
Get your .LA domain today!
www.
.
la
Privacy Policy
TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The following outlines our privacy and data protection policy for this website. Third party partners of TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd, including registry administers of WWW.LA and other websites you may access via this website have different privacy policies and are not subject to this privacy policy. TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd recommends that you read the privacy statement of each such website to find out how they protect your personal information. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Webmaster by e-mail at support@registry.la
Collection and Use of User Details
When you register a domain name or create an account at www.la we may collect personal details about you and any entity you may represent. Personal information such as your name, address, email address and job title is collected via www.la registration forms.
When you visit the www.la site, we also collect web site usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer's IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and, if you arrived at www.la via a link from another website, the URL of the linking page.
We may use this information to:
fulfil orders
personalise the content you will see based on your personal characteristics or preferences
notify you of relevant new products and features on www.la (if you opt in to receiving such information)
notify you of promotions from TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd (if you opt in to receiving such information)
ensure, as far as is practical, that our site is compatible with the browsers and operating systems used by the majority of our visitors.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user's hard drive during a visit to www.la This file allows the user to move quickly and easily around our site. It is used to identify returning users and to identify subscribers and registrants (a registrant - and subscriber - will have the cookie linked to their e-mail address as a way of identifying them). This may means that if you are a registrant or subscriber, you may not have to login each time you visit. We also use a cookie to track a user's sessions. We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so that we can develop TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd in the light of our analysis of people's usage. We also use cookies and the information we collect to show you relevant content.
You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time. Bear in mind, though, that if you delete these cookies, any settings such as your stored username and password will have to be reset when you log in again.
Further information on the use of cookies can be found at www.cookiecentral.com
DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on certain websites operated by TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd, which includes the website www.la. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to these sites, and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:
Google Adsense:
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to serve the advertisements and links that appear on these sites send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd has no access to or control over the cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. The TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Security Policy
TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd has appropriate measures in place to ensure that users' personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within the server environment.
Occasions will arise when customer information is passed outside TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd to other data processors (e.g. fulfilment companies, third party service providers, payment processing or database consultants etc.) but they will only act upon instruction from TLD Registrar Solutions Ltd in order to perform the services required.
Transfer of Personal Data Overseas
Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing www.la and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
Changes to this statement
Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content on www.la we may make changes to our privacy policy and will reflect those changes in this statement, so please check here from time to time.
Copyright © 2014 TLD Registrar Solutions. All Rights Reserved.
By browsing our site, you're agreeing to the use of cookies. Cookies are tiny bits of data websites store in your web browser to make your online experience better.
OK
About
Sell Our Domains
Whois Lookup
FAQs
Policies
Terms of Use
Privacy
© 2020 WWW.LA. All rights reserved.
